Guide to the R.R. Donnelley & Sons Company Archive 1844-2005
University of Chicago Library
- Series III: Company Advertising
  - Subseries 2: General Advertising Samples
    - Printing technology samples, series of six, undated (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Controlled stationery stock inventory system, undated (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Marco Island resort, invitation, hospitality suite, undated (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - "In financial printing…the difference between ordinary and extraordinary is Donnelley," undated (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - National catalog conference, undated (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Short-run books, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - "Crawfordsville 500," sales promotion, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - "An Eye to the Future," recruitment advertisement, undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - General print advertisement, undated (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - "How to Move from Manuscript to Marketplace Faster," undated (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - "You Pay No Extra Overtime Charges," financial printing, undated (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - "Printers Serving a World Demanding Knowledge," recruitment advertisement, undated (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - "Getting More Leads for Your Salesmen," undated (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - "Short Run, Fast Response, Low Cost, In Line Book Printing," undated (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - "Digital Solutions for Book Publishers," undated (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - "Proof for Your OK," insert, undated (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Subseries 3: Scrapbooks
    - RR Donnelley and Weinberg and McKee advertisements in Mill Supplies magazine, ca. 1922-1954 (Box 155)
    - Advertisements and correspondence for supply catalog printing, ca. 1915-1932 (Box 156)
    - Advertisements, 1933-1951 (Box 157)
    - Advertisements, product samples, exhibition catalogs and correspondence, ca. 1929-1933 (Box 158)
  - Subseries 4: Oversize Material
    - "The Model Printing Plant of America," Plymouth Court building, 1909 (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - "Coolidge for Vice President," Fortune magazine insert, 1920 (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - Extra Binding, 1925 (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - Rudolph Ruzicka woodcut sample, 1929 (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - "250 Tons of Type Metal," Fortune magazine insert, 1933 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - "They Came To Us as Schoolboys," Apprentice School, 1933 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - "We still believe that it takes good men to do good work," Fortune magazine insert, 1933 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - "97 trillion," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - "All Under One Roof," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - "Every Tuesday a near miracle," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - "For three months, 2000 men and women kept this million-dollar secret," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - "One good picture beats a thousand words," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - "We are running the wooden Indians out of advertising," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - "We moved Lake Placid to our eighth floor," Fortune magazine insert, 1934 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - "A million-dollar testimonial for some soap maker," Fortune magazine insert, 1935 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - "Ever try to pose a good active baby?" Fortune magazine insert, 1935 (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - "Pictures sell better than words," Fortune magazine insert, 1935 (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - "Your show window at her breakfast table," Fortune magazine insert, 1935 (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - "All under one roof," Fortune magazine insert, 1936 (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - "It’s a far cry from Gutenberg," Fortune magazine insert, 1936 (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - "It takes a lot of brains," Fortune magazine insert, 1936 (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - "Letterpress on Parade," 1936 (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - "Research," Fortune magazine insert, 1936 (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - "Selling fabrics the modern way," direct color photography, 1936 (Box 159, Folder 24)
    - A new specimen Of Donnelley deeptone, Wet Sands painting, Russell Flint, 1937 (Box 159, Folder 25)
    - "Farming is business – big business," Fortune magazine insert, 1937 (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - Gravure and books at the Lakeside Press, 1937 (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - Gravure at the Lakeside Press, Mt. Rainier photograph by Kabel on cover, 1938 (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - "Photo fact printing, effective but low in price," Rockwell Kent illustration, 1938 (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - Sheet fed gravure, Santa Rosa Island photograph by Kabel on cover, 1938 (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - "Snapshots in color," Kodachrome 1, 1938 (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - "Action snapshots in color," Kodachrome 2, 1938 (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - "Travel snapshots in color," Kodachrome 3, 1938 (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - "Flower and fruit prints of the 18th and early 19th century," Fortune magazine insert, 1939 (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - "Sheet fed gravure, a short story," chickens on the cover, 1940 (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - A Comparison - Letterpress, Fine Halftone, Deeptone (One Color), Deeptone (Doubledepth), Gravure (Sheet Fed), three copies, 1936 (Box 161, Folder 1)
    - Advertising tear sheets, 1930s-1960s (Box 161, Folder 2)
    - Sheet fed gravure with annual report insert, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 1)
    - A four color reproduction from a color snapshot, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 2)
    - "Color in modern advertising," Kodachrome 4, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 3)
    - "A different point of view," rotogravure printing, 1939 (Box 162, Folder 4)
    - "More color in modern advertising," Kodachrome 5, 1940 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - "New Specimens of Donnelley Deeptone," using a Mary Cassatt pastel, 1940 (Box 162, Folder 6)
    - "Sheet fed gravure sells more," photograph of a cat by Torkel Korling on cover, 1940 (Box 162, Folder 7)
    - "Direct color photography and modern merchandising," babies on cover, 1940 (Box 162, Folder 8)
    - "America's best customer," letterpress, woman with purse on cover, 1941 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Sheet Fed Gravure, photograph of elephant by Don Wallace, 1941 (Box 163, Folder 2)
    - Gravure sheet fed photographs, photograph of North Dome by Edward Weston, 1941 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - "Catching Your Customer's Eye," sheet fed gravure, 1942 (Box 163, Folder 4)
    - "Ducks Should Look Like Ducks and Dirt Like Dirt," sheet fed gravure, 1947 (Box 163, Folder 5)
    - "Jacob Wrestled With An Angel," Deeptone, 1949 (Box 163, Folder 6)
    - "Jacob Wrestled With An Angel," Deeptone, 1949 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    - "No Ax to Grind," 1948 (Box 164, Folder 2)
    - "Undivided Responsibility," hard binding business campaign 1, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 3)
    - "Have You a Bookbinding Problem?" hard binding business campaign 2, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 4)
    - "Suddenly Comes Spring," sheet fed gravure, hard binding business campaign 3, 1948 (Box 164, Folder 5)
    - Merita Home Service Institute, "Ways to a Woman's Heart" cook book campaign 1, 1949 (Box 164, Folder 6)
    - "Et Cetera," specimens of single-color printing, sheet fed gravure, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Distribution Center, distribution and traffic services, 1949 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    - "Kitchen USA," direct color photography, RR Donnelley studio kitchen, 1950s (Box 165, Folder 3)
    - "Why not consider Donnelley gravure?" booklet, 1950 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Donnelley sheet fed color gravure, 1951 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - "Pictures Plus," Donnelley sheet fed gravure, 1952 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - "Come imagineer with us," Fortune magazine insert, 1952 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - "Having A Wonderful Time," portfolio of photographs, Deeptone, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - "Having A Wonderful Time," portfolio of photographs, Deeptone, 1954 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - "Donnelley Builds a Quality Catalog," 1954 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - Bellingrath Gardens, color photos, Deeptone, 1954 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    - Contrast with Donnelley sheet fed gravure, 1954 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - "SEC printing at Donnelley's," 1955 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    - Cincinnati Milling Machine Company, sheet fed gravure, booklet, 1955 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    - "Freedom of The American Road," Ford Motor Company, magazine, 1956 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    - "At the Flick of the Finger" and "Underling Steel," Basic Refractories, Inc., sheet fed gravure, 1956 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    - "What's Happening in Chicago," Chicago Central Area Committee, gravure, 1956 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    - Apollo II booklet with Life and Look photos, Deeptone, 1969 (Box 170, Folder 1)
    - "Birds in Porcelain," a demonstration of fine printing, 1970 (Box 170, Folder 2)
    - "The inside story on circulars is inside," 1970s (Box 170, Folder 3)
    - "Par for the Course," catalogs, 1970s (Box 170, Folder 4)
    - "Adventure Road Takes the Expressway to Success," magazine, 1973 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    - "Here’s the full story about tabloid inserts," 1973 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    - Telephone directory production, electronic graphics division, 1975 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    - "Put Yourself in the Winner’s Circle," directories, 1976 (Box 170, Folder 8)
    - "Looking For A Good Idea? We've Got Two," catalog and magazine inserts, 1976 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Web offset printing, general information, 1976 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Electronic Graphics, 1977 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - "The Drawing Board, Inc.," Selectronic update, mailing 1, 1978 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - 23 copies of "A Small Road at Yabu Koji Atagoshita by Hiroshige," print and associated literature, 1978-1979 (Box 172)
    - Radio Shack Flyer, Selectronic Update, Mailing 4, 1979 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - "Think Dwight," Dwight Printing Services, 1981 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - Advertising tear sheets, 1980s-1990s (Box 173, Folder 3)
    - "Thin books," adding value to books, 1980s (Box 173, Folder 4)
    - "How to read beyond the dots," adding value to catalogs, 1980s (Box 173, Folder 5)
    - Chicago Bar Association, financial printing, 1983 (Box 173, Folder 6)
    - "80 Pine," magazine advertisement, 1983 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    - "Fort Worth," financial printing, 1983 (Box 173, Folder 8)
    - DMMA, invitation, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - "Magazine production – is there more to expanding capacity than brick and mortar?" magazine ad, 1978 (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - "Are you ready for the one-subscriber magazine?" magazine ad, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - "Can a printer add value to your publication?" magazine ad, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - "If you know what it costs," book ad, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Radio Shack flyer, Selectronic update, mailing 4, 1979 (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Selectronic, 1980 (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Harrisonburg posters, book advertisements, 1981 (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - "Pull Yourself Together," DMMA Invitation, make your own mask, 1982 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Book advertisements, 1983-1984 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - "Adding Value to Books," 1985 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - "Capture the Look," Lancaster offset, 1985 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - "Capture the Look," Lancaster offset, 1985-1986 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Selectronic, 1985 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - "Adding Value to Magazines," Advertising Age insert, 1985 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - "It’s a small thing," adding value to catalogs, 1985 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - "The financial fast track now has a passing lane," financial printing services, 1987 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - "A portrait of yet another satisfied customer," financial, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - "For those who set the pace," financial, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - "Introducing a great place to get out of fast," financial, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - "Vision and reality – Mark Levine of American Baby," magazines, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - "Vision and reality – Rob Wood of Modern Maturity," magazines 1988 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Vision and reality – Tom Emanuel of the World Wrestling Federation," magazines, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - "Vision and Reality – Irv Herschbein of Condé Nast," magazines, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - "How to get wrinkles out of your Old Testament," Bibleworks, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - "Less is not more – Noah’s Ark," book printing, 1988 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - "Less is not more – ballet," book printing, 1989-1990 (Box 177, Folder 1)
    - "Less is not more – Jack," book printing, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 2)
    - "Less is not more – Vincent," book printing, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 3)
    - "Heaven forbid you should want to make any edition changes," Bibleworks book printing, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 4)
    - "How to get to church on time," Bibleworks book printing, 1989 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - "Envision," 1991 (Box 177, Folder 6)
    - "Leverage," technical documentation services, 1992 (Box 177, Folder 7)
    - Direct marketing party, New York, undated (Box 178, Folder 1)
    - Book printing, undated (Box 178, Folder 2)
    - "Magazine marketing - Is it time to make your magazine worth more?" undated (Box 178, Folder 3)
    - Publisher's Weekly, book printing, undated (Box 178, Folder 4)
    - "When it's printed by Donnelley, it's on sale on time," book printing, undated (Box 178, Folder 5)
    - "Why a special interest magazine should have a printer it can't outgrow," undated (Box 178, Folder 6)
    - Advertising tear sheet display book, undated (Box 178, Folder 7)
    - "Exploding Ink!" heat-set printing, undated (Box 178, Folder 8)
    - Extra Binding, Plymouth Court, undated (Box 178, Folder 9)
    - Inserts, photocopies, undated (Box 178, Folder 10)
    - "Religious Printing at Donnelley's," Crawfordsville, undated (Box 178, Folder 11)
    - Bibleworks, undated (Box 178, Folder 12)
    - "Capture Your Look," Lancaster plant, undated (Box 178, Folder 13)
    - "East Meets West," 1964 (Box 179, Folder 1)
    - Software publishers association, 1987 (Box 179, Folder 2)
    - Bibleworks, undated (Box 179, Folder 3)
    - Catalog Services Group, undated (Box 179, Folder 4)
    - Direct Marketing party, "Twinkle Twinkle" invitation, undated (Box 179, Folder 5)
    - DMA reception, Washington, D.C., undated (Box 179, Folder 6)
    - "Happily Ever After: A New Way of Looking at Children’s Books," undated (Box 179, Folder 7)
    - "How to know where your most profitable responses are coming from," undated (Box 179, Folder 8)
    - "How to recognize your hottest prospects," undated (Box 179, Folder 9)
    - "Ideas often start out small and fragile," Face-to-face Publishing Exposition, undated (Box 179, Folder 10)
    - "If mystery is your mood…" undated (Box 179, Folder 11)
    - "Man for the Ages," Abraham Lincoln portrait, undated (Box 179, Folder 12)
    - "Mark Levine of American Baby on how to grow a magazine," undated (Box 179, Folder 13)
    - Modern Maturity, undated (Box 179, Folder 14)
    - "New York Time," National Catalog Conference party invitation, undated (Box 179, Folder 15)
    - Savina uncial typeface, undated (Box 179, Folder 16)
    - "Tom Emanuel of the World Wrestling Federation on the power of flexibility," undated (Box 179, Folder 17)
    - "You’ll find new ideas of all kinds," Face-to-face Publishing Exposition, undated (Box 179, Folder 18)
    - "Young Woman with Water Jug," Vermeer reproduction, undated (Box 179, Folder 19)
- Series IV: Customers and Products
  This series collects RR Donnelley's files on its customers, including products (usually called "job samples") that it printed for them. These samples number in the thousands, and are found in several subseries of this series. This series also includes business records such as contracts and agreements, correspondence, photographs, and collections of historical background material on individual customers. This series has been divided into four subseries; while similar types of material can be found across these subseries, each subseries has a distinctly different organizational structure.
  Subseries 1: Customer Files, includes material on many of RR Donnelley's clients, such as Time-Life, Inc., Sears Roebuck and Company, and Encyclopaedia Britannica, Inc. Material in this subseries is arranged alphabetically by client name or product title, and includes job samples, contracts and agreements, correspondence, photographs, and historical background material. Samples of mass-market magazines such as Life, Time, People, Business Week, and Fortune are found in this series. Samples of products tend to be selective, rather than comprehensive. Oversize material from this subseries has been transferred to Subseries 5.
  Subseries 2: Customer Job Samples, collects samples of products printed for an enormous number of clients, from international corporations to small businesses, clubs and individuals. Catalogs, brochures, books, broadsides, periodicals, and packaging are among the more common types of material in this subseries. Library catalog cards, memos, and other supporting material are occasionally found filed with the samples. While the date range of this subseries extends from the late nineteenth to early twenty-first century, most of the samples in this subseries date from the 1920s-1950s. This subseries is arranged alphabetically, usually by the name of the client or the client's product, but occasionally by the title of the product. Material filed under personal names may be found under either the first or last name of the individual (for example, items produced for the Marshall Field department stores are found under both "Marshall Field" and "Field, Marshall." Oversize material from this subseries has been transferred to Subseries 5.
  Subseries 3: Subject File, contains material similar to that found in the previous two subseries, such as job samples, correspondence, contracts, and historical background material. However, material in this series is arranged alphabetically by subject, rather than by customer or product. Typical subjects include events such as the 1984 Olympic Games; memorial publications for celebrated individuals such as Princess Diana; broad product types such as telephone directories; and units of the company such as the Intervisual Communications group. Material included in this subseries is generally distinguished by its topicality, historical significance or aesthetic quality. Oversize material from this subseries has been transferred to Subseries 5.
  Subseries 5: Oversize Material and Artifacts, contains job samples, proofs, ledgers, printing plates, and other large-format material transferred from Subseries 1-3. This material can be traced to its original subseries location through the descriptive headings.
  Additional samples of products that RR Donnelley printed for clients are found throughout the collection, but particularly in Series IX and XII. Records related to RR Donnelley's business relationships with clients can also be found in Series II, VII, VII, VIII and XI. The photographs in Series XI include images of customer jobs in production, as well as visits of clients to RR Donnelley facilities; this same series also includes oral history recordings that discuss RR Donnelley's relationships to clients.
  - Subseries 1: Customer Files
    - American Bible Society, rights to exclusive use of bold face Bible Monotype matrices, 1930-1945 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    - Arthur H. Clark Company, Early Western Travels series, 1958 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    - Automotive, Ford and General Motors, office correspondence, 1969 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    - Bergstrom, Evangeline, "Old Glass Paperweights," 1940-1941 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    - Brooks, Reverend A., invoice, 1873 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    - Business Week, 1968-1989 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    - Business Week, job samples, 1979-1988 (Box 180, Folder 7-10)
    - Business Week, job samples, 1989-1990 (Box 181, Folder 1-5)
    - Callaghan & Co., request for quote, 1903 (Box 181, Folder 6)
    - Chicago Magazine, 1978-1988 (Box 181, Folder 7-8)
    - Chicago Magazine, 1982 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Magazine, job samples, 1986-1987 (Box 182, Folder 2-7)
    - Chicago Magazine, job samples, 1987-1990 (Box 183, Folder 1-3)
    - Chicago Natural History Museum, 1949 (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Compton, F.E., 1938-1984 (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Compton, F.E., Compton's Pictured Encyclopedia, contract, 1954 (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - Compton, F.E., contract changes, 1956-1961 (Box 183, Folder 7)
    - Compton, F.E., photographs for article on book making, 1969 (Box 183, Folder 8)
    - Compton, F.E., style guide, undated (Box 183, Folder 9)
    - Condé Nast Publications, negotiations, 1936 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Condé Nast Publications, 1960-1981 (Box 184, Folder 2-4)
    - Cowles Communications, Look, 1948-1979 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Cowles Communications, Family Circle, 1958-1991 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Cowles Communications, Family Circle and Look magazines, Mattoon plant tour, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    - Cowles Communications, Family Circle, plant tour and dedication, photographs, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    - Cowles Communications, memo and Donnelley Printer tear sheets, 1982-1984 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    - Cowles Communications, job samples, 1968-1991 (Box 185, Folder 1-3)
    - Cowles Communications, job samples, 1982-1989 (Box 185, Folder 4-5)
    - Crain Communications, 1996 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Dun & Broadstreet, 1953-1990 (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, dinner programs, 1910-1911 (Box 185, Folder 8)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, Charles Crawford Whinery, specification notebook, 1915-1917 (Box 185, Folder 9)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, specifications, correspondence, 1919 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, liquidation proposal, 1919-1938 (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, excerpts from minutes books, 1920-1946 (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, RR Donnelley announcement of 14th edition, 1929 (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1931-1979 (Box 186, Folder 5-6)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, Franklin H. Hooper, "Story of the Encyclopaedia Britannica," 1939 (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, "passport" dinner programs for Book of the Year party, 1939 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, W. Alison Phillips, photostat of typescript, ca. 1940s (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, photographs, ca. 1940s-1960s (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, printing agreement and changes, 1955 (Box 186, Folder 11)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, printing agreement changes, 1957-1960 (Box 187, Folder 1-3)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, Robert E. Wood, A Monument for the World, 1963 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, tribute book honoring William Benton, correspondence and design samples, 1965 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, special issue of Donnelley Printer featuring Encyclopaedia Britannica entry for "Flight," 1968 (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 200th anniversary event program and photographs, 1968 (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, Britannica 3 presentation, 1973-1974 (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Encyclopaedia Britannica, loss of account, 1981 (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Farm Journal, bound sample issue, 1921 (Box 187, Folder 10)
    - Farm Journal, sample issue, 1922 (Box 187, Folder 11)
    - Farm Journal, bound sample issues, 1933-1950 (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Farm Journal, photographs, ca. 1935-1941 (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Farm Journal, 1935-1986 (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Farm Journal, printing agreement, 1958 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Farm Journal, job samples, 1935-1979 (Box 189, Folder 4-8)
    - Farm Journal, job samples, 1985-1990 (Box 190, Folder 1-3)
    - Fortune, 1948 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Fortune, printing agreement, 1958 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - George T. Brodnax, Inc., 1948 (Box 190, Folder 6)